

Nenad Milosevic aka Kirf

Designer, Co-Founder and Producer Belgrade, Serbia

Profile

My love for computer graphics started very early on when I figured out how to draw and trace logos in *Electronic Arts DeluxePaint* software running on an old *Amiga 1200* I bought in 1994 (I was just 12 at that time). I switched to PC in 1999 and continued exploring and learning even more about computer graphics and design, so I created *DeviantArt* profile in the beginning of 2002. In 2007 I started my carrier as freelance designer...

With almost 10 years of professional designing experience in web design and user interfaces, I have the creative solutions to increase user experience and usability, bring user interface to the edge of industry standards and make it look and feel modern and professional.

Experience

2014 - Present: Co-founder @ Bipbop Games (2 employees)

Started a company with a friend. Designing, illustrating and animating games. Making tunes and sound FX. Participating in game design. Creating motion graphics and promo videos. Managing social networks. http://bipbopgames.com

2011 - Present: **Designer @ Infobip (Centili)** (500 - 1000 employees) Designing & coding websites & user interfaces on variety of in-house mobile and web payment pages, widgets, libraries and panels. Given full responsibility over some projects. Participating in product design as well. https://www.centili.com | https://www.infobip.com

2009 - 2011: **Designer @ Ladybug Communications** (5 - 10 employees) Coding, designing and animating websites, web components, banners and presentations in Adobe Flash.

2007 - 2011: **Freelance Designer @ MaxNova Creative** (5 - 10 employees) Coding, designing and animating websites, web components, banners and presentations in Adobe Flash.

http://www.maxnova.rs

http://www.ladybug.rs

2007 - Present: Freelance Designer

Designing websites, banners, promo material, brochures, cd covers, mobile apps, animating, illustrating and creating motion graphics for over 100 clients all over the world.

http://therootout.com

Details

16/09/1982 +381 63 377315 rootout@gmail.com http://therootout.com

Skills

Design

UI design, User Experience, Web Design, Interaction Design, Usability Testing, Game Design, Illustrations, Graphic Design, Branding, Product Design, Mobile/App Design for Android and iOS, Flash

Front end development

HTML, CSS, JS, ActionScript, PHP

Video

Animations, Motion Graphics

Sound

Production, Composing, Sound Synthesis, Arranging, Mastering

Languages

English (full professional proficiency), Serbian (Native)

Other

Scrum, Git, SEO & ASO, Assets Optimization...

Education

Self-taught in all things design, development and music production :) 2000 - Present

High Technical School "Nikola Tesla" (Electronics) 1996 - 2000

Other Passions

1996 - Present: **Producer @ The Root Out** (1 - 5 members)
I started making beats on my old **Commodore Amiga** in 1996 using software like **OctaMED** and **NoiseTracker** for arrangements and production and **TurboTechno Sound** for sampling. From beginning till now few people have been in **The Root Out** playing different instruments, singing and writing tunes. To this day I'm continuing to make noise and experiment with a sound.

http://therootout.com

Awards

Digital art festival "ArtTech" 1st place in static design (2007). Work published in *Svet Komjutera* (1/2008).